Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
Croatia.
[music]
A beautiful country with a long scenic
coast on the Adriatic Sea. Known for
delicious seafood, charming harbors with
centuries of history, stunning national
parks, and lively culture.
Heat up
>> [music]
[music]
>> here.
[music] Heat. Heat. N.
[music]
Heat. Heat. N.
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hallelujah.
Okay.
Heat. Heat. N.
>> [music]
>> Heat. Hey, heat. Hey, heat.
[music]
Mhm.
>> [music]
>> Baby boy.
Very [music] soft.
Where is it?
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
>> Hello.
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I don't [music] want to anymore.
>> [music]
>> Hey Sassini Dr. Squad, how are you? How
you doing? We are in Croatia.
I am in a city called Zagreb. [music] I
believe this is the capital. Don't quote
me. I'll clarify on the screen. [music]
So, if you've never seen me before, my
name is Dr. Linda Moni. If you haven't
and you're part of the squad, welcome
back. [music]
So, y where do I begin? [music] Uh, we
started the journey yesterday. I think
the last thing you guys saw was when I
was at the dinner [music] and that's
part of the package of this trip. This
trip is called Euro Trip Soft. Not to be
confused with [music]
Euro Trip. Sour. Euro trip is just Euro
trip and then this is Euro [music] Trip
Soft. and Euro trip the difference is
I'll put the list of the countries that
you go to when you go uh for Euro trip
but there are about eight countries um
and then for this trip you do 2 weeks
it's more or less it's more or less like
2 weeks and you do only four countries
but for Euro trip you do eight countries
in 3 weeks so it's very hectic we had a
dinner at um Upper Hill uh not Upper
Hill sorry at Radison Aboretam and Then
uh we started our journey yesterday. We
left Nairobi at exactly 6:00 p.m. We
flew with Qatar economy. You get economy
seats very comfortable. We had so many
meals guys. Yo, as in I felt like every
two every two minutes Qatar was feeding
us something. I'm not complaining though
cuz I mean you have the option to say
no. So we left Nairobi yesterday at 6:00
p.m. and then we got to Doha. We had a
connective flight now from Doha to
Croatia. So we got to it's about 5 hours
give or take from Nairobi to Doha and
then from Doha to Croatia is also
another 5 hours. So we've been traveling
the whole night basically. My eye bags
are y on another level. Um I would say
I'm tired but I'm also very excited to
be in a new country. And then guess
what? So the lady that I'm rooming with,
hopefully she'll agree to be on camera.
If not, I will completely respect that.
Apparently, she found out about Wavu and
went for the Euro trip last year because
of my vlog. So, I was like, "Oh my god,
this is so heartwarming." So, I've
already gotten to know a couple of
people on this trip. We're very few, by
the way. We are only 18. That's also
another difference um between Eurosoft
and Euro Trip. As it is right now,
Eurosoft, we're only 18 people. So,
there's a lot of space in the bus. You
know, it's a manageable crowd. um you
know and also like I said the itinerary
is very slow and soft and I will show
you guys because we're going to four
countries four okay and then for Euro
trip um we were many we were around 60
people so
you know in a jar so I've already met a
couple of babes from the group and we've
had a really nice kiki you guys have
seen downstairs we got here at the hotel
around 7:00 no we got to the airport
around 7:00 but we've gotten to the
hotel around 8:00 something. Uh we came
upstairs, took a drop bags, went
downstairs, had breakfast. This trip
only covers for your accommodation, the
activities, and breakfast. So, lunch and
dinner is on you. The plan is to shower,
get dressed, look really nice and cute.
At a I look tired, so I need to do
something with my hair. I'm not sure if
this is what I'll still go with. find a
nice cute outfit to wear and then maybe
go meet one of the one of the guys one
of the guys in the trip in the group. We
go maybe have a drink as we wait for the
activity in the afternoon. We're
supposed to go for an for like a city
tour in the afternoon. So yeah, let's
get ready together. Let's do that. I
have my speaker going. Um by the day
this trip I really packed like ni panga
visor. Let let me even show you. Let me
show you for those of you who wonder
what to pack for some of these things.
So, everything is already out. So,
please excuse there's a bit of mess
because I was already um I had already
started unpacking. I got this bag, this
um packing bags from China Square. I
think each was going for like 600
[music] bob. And in here I have a small
pack that has all the medication. This
would be painkillers,
um ant acids, um something for
allergies, just medication like that.
Emodium things that you would need need
when you're traveling. And then this is
just jewelry in here. Like it's just a
bag that has jewelry.
And then this has my makeup brushes.
This little bag here.
It has my makeup brushes. And then this
is all my makeup obviously by pharmacy.
Um on this side I have more so hair
care. So this this side is for my skin
and then this side is hair. I have Okay.
Yeah, this is also for my skin. Sorry
but this is just sunscreen. I have um
aries which is basically like the only
oil I use for my body. And then a couple
of other things just hair care ni and
double-sided tape in case I need it. And
then I also have another bag similar to
that one where I packed shoes. I packed
my shoes separately here. And in here I
have very specific pair of shoes. I have
a pair of sandals. And then I have a
pair of black heels that obviously go
with everything. And a pair of walking
walking shoes. This type of shoes. And I
put the socks for walking in there. But
this is um this is what I got. I got
these shoes from Sheen. And I decided to
get this because I didn't want to be
walking around with um like sport shoes
aesthetic you know outfits. So I opted
to get those walking shoes. Yeah. Then
of course now here we have like my inner
wear and this is just a night dress and
my camera. This suitcase as you can see
is not very full. So I didn't pack a lot
of things and that was very intentional.
As you guys remember,
even for the Euro trip ship, I came with
my suitcase half empty because I knew I
would be shopping. And that's exactly
the same thing I've done even this year.
So, I have two suitcases.
I have this one and then I also have
this one. This is the bigger one, right?
And let me just open so you guys can
see. On this side, it's completely empty
because I know I'll obviously be
shopping and I don't want to like exceed
my what is it called? My weight at the
airport. Oh,
something else something else I need to
mention about uh Eurosoft.
When it comes to moving from country to
country with Euro trip, we were moving
through Europe in a bus all the way from
Germany to Spain in a bus. But for
Eurosoft, we are either when within a
country, we're moving around in a bus,
the big black bus that you guys saw,
which is very comfortable. It's
spacious.
And then when we're moving from country
to country, we are taking flights. We
had already been told that there's a
weight restriction of 36 kgs when we're
moving from one country to the next. So
yeah, that's why I didn't want to
overpack. But basically, this is what I
have. I want to we'll be here for 3 days
so I want to at least move some things
from this corner to the bathroom. I need
to shower. My roommate has gone to the
mall but for me I was like guys
no I need some time alone. I'm usually
especially in such groups I need some
time alone. I was just like no let me
just take some time. Uh I shower to poly
poly. I get ready put on a bit of makeup
decide what I'm going to wear. Iron it
and things like that. So let's get to
it. And also, by the way, let me show
you guys something about my my view
right here. These are train rails. And
I've actually seen a couple of trains
passing by while I was uh recording.
Anyway, let's get to it.
[music and singing]
[music]
Cuz
I'm looking for never backtracking
[music]
on memory lane hoping it's not just
[singing] the one
I can't be watching waiting for changes
want to run for the right time
cuz I [singing] notice [music] we came
to a pavement that crumbles it's just a
[singing] merry go around I don't I
think it's [music] you,
might be me.
There's just so many things going on.
But when I'm [music] with you,
it feels so new.
Cuz I'm on a secret. I'm all alone for
I've been [music] off and on with you.
Tell me why it's so hard to choose.
Going in circles round and round
[singing]
[music] cuz I'm looking for never
backtracking on memories. Hoping [music]
it's not just a wonder.
I can't be watching waiting for changes.
Wondering for the right time.
Cuz I notice [music] we came to a
pavement that crumbles. It's just a
merrygo [music and singing]
round. I don't think it's you.
Might be me.
There's [music and singing] just so many
things going on. But when I'm with you,
[music]
it feels so new.
Cuz I'm on a secret. I'm all [music]
alone. I don't think it's [singing] you.
Might be me. [music]
Oh, there's just so many things going
on. So many things with you. Yeah.
[music]
Cuz I'm honestly right. I fall in love.
Here they are. Everything is from Sheen.
Everything from head to toe. And my two
shoes that I love so much. These shorts
are folding over here. And I think it's
because
but
it's fine. Like there's nothing I can do
right now. Maybe I just try to
What can I do? Whatever. Let's go have a
drink downstairs as we wait for uh the
walking tour. [music]
[singing]
>> Shot of the train.
>> And then also this drink. It has gym
procco and I can't remember what it is.
It's so nice. Like it's smooth. It's
sweet, strong. Exactly what you want for
the hall.
[music]
>> [music]
>> is the largest city.
[music]
Yeah.
Heat. [music]
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat.
Fing.
[music]
Heat. Heat. N.
Awaken
[music]
in silence. [music]
The light in my eyes barely surviving.
It's making me feel I'm alone on the
silent [music] lost in the labyrinth.
It's weighing me down. And all of the
[music] sirens are waiting forever. They
drive me insane. [singing]
No way. [music] Every time I take a
step, I get closer to [singing] the
edge. But
>> good morning squ outfit of the day.
I have this set from Sheen and
[music]
>> um I've already carried I've also
carried my swimsuit. I forgotten my
sunglasses, but I've carried my swimsuit
and
um what else?
Yeah, sorry. I don't know why my brain
is not computing. I think it's cuz time
is up and I haven't had breakfast. I had
gone back to the room because I forgot
my battery, extra battery for this
camera. And then I've left my things
here very irresponsibly at the reception
right here. Please don't do that. Be
more responsible than me.
But so far,
so far I've not gotten any like vibes of
insecurity in Croatia. In fact, the
people are extremely friendly. But for
now, I need to rush at least see if I
can get something to eat. I won't vlog
that. I'm sorry. I'm in a rush. Toodles.
>> I made it on the bus. I managed to have
breakfast.
Then you guys remember the drink that I
found Jana at the mall?
>> It's right here. The one that's Oh,
wait. No. Did I show you? I didn't show
you guys. So, Jana, after we shopped uh
for clothes and all that, we passed by
the supermarket and we decided to get
dressed because we are
>> open.
So, we're heading to Slovenia in Croatia
and it's a 2-hour drive.
>> Look at this.
>> Amazing.
>> [music]
>> So we just came from Croatia.
We drove 2 hours from Zagreb to
Ljubljana which is in Slovenia. We are
currently doing the city tour. The vibes
and I'll update you as we as we go. I
have my walking shoes. I have my water.
I'm ready.
>> I was done with [music] the chase, done
with the games. Gave up on love and I
was lost in a dark. So used to being
alone at home [music] with no one to
hold. Out of luck. Was tired of all of
the wasted nights. [music]
But you out of the blue
like an angel I can see from afar.
>> We're now on a boat ride, a city boat
ride, and then we'll go for the cruise.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Yeah,
[music]
heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I feel
Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat up here.
[music]
We've done the city tour and then we've
gone for the boat ride you guys have
seen. Then we've stopped to buy
souvenirs. [music] So I came to use a
washroom and now we're going back to the
bus and we go to like blend. So I'll
show you. Hopefully I get some drinks.
>> [music]
>> else.
>> Earlier there is a church I can't
remember the name but we went to that
church and took pictures and it wasn't
it wasn't what I was looking for because
it was a bit gloomy in the morning and
now the sun is out. As much as this is
horrible weather to walk in, obviously
you guys know if you're coming for Euro
trip, please don't carry even a single
jacket, even a shaw, even a scarf,
nothing. Uh we went back to take
pictures, right? The pictures right now,
we took so many pictures in the morning,
but right now to like four, three
pictures, they look so nice. There's
just something about taking pictures on
vacation and the sun is out. It's not
the same as when it's gloomy. So, I'm
just happy we went back. And like I
said, this is horrible weather to walk
in. It's very hot. Please carry your
sunscreen if you do come. Sunscreen,
sunglasses, hats, um light clothing. I
love this set that I'm wearing. It's
very light. Like I'm not even feeling
like your excessive heat as much as it
looks like it's um it's a very uh warm
outfit. So,
okay, we're being called to go. Go
see [music]
a queen.
When I'm alone, I'm [music]
let the phone [singing] keep quiet.
Quiet. [music]
It's me time. Sweet [music] time. Let me
see.
in my socks like it's [music] the
headlight
hey [music]
[music]
down
Hey, Terry Squad. So, we just got back
to the hotel from Slovenia, and it's
been like a 2-hour drive. It was fun. I
had I had a really good time. Um, so
right now it's 8:32, but the sun is
still out. Looks like it's maybe it
could be maybe 6:00 p.m. in Kenya or
5:30. want to go downstairs, have
dinner, and then we'll come back because
tomorrow we're supposed to check out and
we have to take a flight to the next
country. [music]
[music]
Good morning, dear cards. I'm here with
the with my roomie. [laughter]
So, we are going to the mall. We're
supposed to leave um the city today of Z
Grab and go to Drognik.
>> Yeah. So, we're supposed to catch a
flight. But for now, we are
[clears throat] heading to the mall.
It's a 5minut walk and I'm going with my
room because she's been there.
>> So, she kind of knows where we're going.
Well, she kind of she actually knows
where we're going.
>> Nie.
>> [laughter]
>> It's this way. Wow.
[laughter]
But I understand force of habit.
>> So yeah. Um, what can I say? First of
all, before we Okay, ideally, I'm only
going to the mall because I really want
to get silk dresses. Hopefully some more
things for like the outfits for the
trip. I already have like majority of
the outfits, but I don't mind adding a
couple of things. We've already checked
out. So, when we go to the when we come
back from the mall, it's just putting
things in our suitcases, which are at
the reception, and then we leave.
>> Thought I had to try to make no
mistakes. [singing]
I prep
[music]
the mood. [singing] Greet them with a
smile. I
thought that it was smart. Stay
[singing] in my lane. Always hit the
mark. Thought that was the way to get a
head start. Perfection's [music] the
play. I had the leading part.
I realize you never get a medal
[singing] in the end. No, no one's going
to give you [music] any credit. I
[singing] was playing a game when no one
else seemed [music] to participate. And
I can't believe I got so judgy.
I [music] don't know what got into me.
Can't believe I let it get so ugly.
I let it go [singing and music]
too far. Got so touchy.
Thinking nobody got me. Can't believe I
[singing] let it get so hard.
Let it go [singing]
[music] too far and slow.
Overwork every situation. Keeping
[music] track of what everybody's doing.
>> So this is the third outfit. We have an
all black party. This is what I'll be
wearing. Outfit styled and recommended
by Agnes, the one and only,
[laughter]
>> but I need to size up on the shorts
again.
>> [music]
>> I was playing
>> 1 2 3 4 5 [music]
>> Yeah, that one is
>> I think it's supposed to be one [music]
like this. But
yeah, I don't have a
[music and singing]
So
check it.
[laughter]
>> The last outfit
>> color is so good on your skin tone.
>> Yeah.
[music]
>> The last outfit for the airport.
>> So cute.
I'm glad it fits perfectly. Have some
ones.
[music]
>> I love how like a snatched
Yeah,
>> it's really nice and it's so soft. Give
me a pull back and then I
wear
>> I like that.
>> I don't
let me show them.
Why?
[music and singing]
Don't know what to me. Can't believe I
let it get [music] so worth it.
[music]
We have checked in. I'm having lunch. I
just got a teriyaki box.
[music]
>> [music]
>> We are now waiting to board to leave for
the Robnik and so far let me tell you
we've been to Slovenia. I'm sure you
guys have seen so far we've been to
Slovenia and we've been in Croatia for
the last 2 days. We'll be in Republic
Robnik for 4 days and the people here
are so friendly. They are so friendly.
You actually don't feel black. They
don't stare. They don't treat you
anyhow. They're so nice. This trip it's
very easy. Like it's not as hectic as
the other Euro trip that Wavo has. Not
that it's bad, but the other one, you
know, you do eight countries in 3 weeks.
This one we're doing four countries in
like almost 2 weeks cuz it's like 14
days. Am I 13 days? There about 14 days.
Yeah. So basically 2 weeks. It's very
slow, very chill. We woke up. We went to
the mall.
We've been here since um I think around
midday. We're waiting for a flight to
board and then we go to the next
destination. So yeah, I would for me
personally up until now this is this is
more my speed. I should have come for
this. In fact,
it's the same price as the other one,
but you can't compare in terms of value.
Like the rooms are so nice. The bus that
we're riding in will not.
So yeah, that's my experience so far.
anything like this.
[music]
>> I can feel it, feel [music] it, feel it
in my [singing] body.
With you,
I can feel it, feel it, feel in my mind.
Do I look back strong? [music]
Just trying to do more supernova with
you.
Yeah, she knows I'm feeling do [music]
it back
now. Can I do [singing] it back? Yeah,
do it back. Tell me, tell me what you
need right now. [music]
I just want that. Do it. [singing]
Do it.
Tell me, tell me what [music] you need
right now. I just want that. Do a look.
Do a look.